What's that song called?
The one everyone sang at Azha's wedding.
Which one? Hum a few bars.
Oh, I know.
This...
Hello?
Where are you?
Just passed Xigui.
You'll be there before dark.
What time will we get here?
Around nightfall.
How am I supposed to
know when it gets dark?
Stop.
Bro.
Is it okay if you stay
at my friend's place?
Is the room ready?
Yeah. How long is he staying?
He didn't say.
He won't be staying long.
Alright, just take him there first.
I'm off.
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
(Episode 1: DJI)
Thanks for your hard work.
This is the laundry room.
This is the kitchen.
This is the dining room.
You can have tea here.
Don't be picky.
You're lucky to have a place to stay.
And Brother Guo is in Shangjing.
You're slumming it in the tea
mountains without an assistant this time?
Aren't you my assistant?
Let me make this clear.
I'm your brother.
Not your assistant.
Brother equals assistant.
When your assistant gets here, I'm out.
Take it. We're going to the master's
place tomorrow night to roast tea.
Okay, I'm off.
I'll show you to your room.
How old are you?
18?
You're asking me?
Take a guess.
You look 80.
Uh, inside.
Sister Lan.
Hey, Lu.
There are two boxes of props over there.
Could you call the props
team to move them for me?
Okay.
Should I answer it?
Who is it?
Sister Lan.
Answer it.
I'll hold it for you.
Qinglang.
Sister Lan, I'm in the shower.
You're in Molie?
Just got here.
Did you get carsick?
Yeah, I was throwing up like crazy.
Come back. There's water.
Is someone with you?
Uh, Qingtian.
He's holding the phone for me.
Alright then.
If you're not comfortable,
just stay for a couple of days.
We need you for a cameo
in the scenes there next week.
About the variety show with Shi Yuhao...
If you have second thoughts, let me know.
I'll handle it.
Okay.
Lu, call the props team to move this.
Sister Lan, I don't want to be on set.
Lang Di needs me.
How can I not be by his side?
Lang Di has a new assistant.
Who knows Lang Di better than I do?
If I'm not with him,
he can't even eat or sleep properly.
Alright, just take good
care of those two handfuls.
I couldn't care less about Qi Haoyu.
He's not even with our agency.
Don't be childish.
If we can't be childish now,
we'll be too old for it, Sister Lan.
Mm.
Lang Di just agreed to do the variety show.
Shi Yuhao will definitely
be haunting him now.
I have to be by his
side at a time like this.
I'm going downstairs to cook.
I'll call you when dinner's ready.
Hello.
Sorry, I don't drink iced beverages.
The actors have left for the set.
Cut the act.
Are you out of your mind?
Why would you do a
variety show with Shi Yuhao?
Lang Di, are you being held hostage?
Ah, this is great!
My Leopard and Kitty are reuniting!
Bro, are you short on cash?
To think you'd even take this show.
Bro, did the agency
make you take this show?
I don't want to see you
get used by Shi Yuhao again.
A seven-year love affair
ends for a new flame.
Ah, I'm going crazy!
Do you need help getting dressed?
Mm.
[A string of unintelligble
hashtags on Weibo maybe?]
[Xu the God of Wealth is calling]
Are you okay?
I heard you went into the
mountains with Qingtian.
[Shi Yuhao is calling]
If you hadn't answered, I
was about to come find you.
Brother Guo.
Oh, Sister Lan.
Oh, Sister Lan, hello.
I've heard so much about you.
Hello, hello. Thank you for your hard work.
This kid insisted on going to Molie.
Brother Guo, go get Han Lu's costume ready.
Han Lu.
I was just on the phone with him.
I heard a stranger's voice with him.
He said it was Qingtian.
But the voice didn't sound like him.
Did Qingtian tell you who's
hosting them over there?
They're all Qingtian's tea farmer friends.
Is it safe?
No one's chasing
celebrities in the mountains.
Oh, that's good. I'll let
you get back to work.
Bro, let me.
Qingtian said he's not with you.
So where are you staying?
At a villager's house.
Is it safe?
What about dinner?
You were sleeping so soundly,
I didn't want to wake you.
Hey, you changed your clothes.
I only wear pajamas when I sleep.
How did my clothes get changed?
How would I know?
I'm hungry.
Be careful what you eat in the mountains.
You have a sensitive stomach.
You'll throw up if you don't eat well.
I hear the food there is on the spicy side.
Tell Qingtian to go easy on the spice.
Qingtian isn't cooking for me.
Who is, then?
My assistant.
Brother Guo being there is fine too.
Come down.
I heated it up in the microwave.
See if it's too hot.
Let go.
You want me to feed you?
Mm-hmm.
Open your mouth.
Wider.
Mm.
Tea or coffee?
They have coffee here?
They produce both tea and coffee here.
Whatever.
They don't produce 'whatever'.
Qinglang, talk to me.
Before we film the show,
if you harass me again,
I'll break the contract.
I'm not trying to harass you.
I'm just worried about you.
Worried about what?
I know you.
You agreed to do this show so readily.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You want to have your cake and eat it too.
The way you're acting
right now disgusts me.
We can't sort this out over the phone.
Where are you?
I'm in hell. Come and get me if you dare.
[Zhang Fengdan is calling]
Hello, Sister Dan.
I'm on set.
Shooting a short commercial.
Hey, Yuhao's back.
Yuhao, when are you and
Qinglang doing that variety show?
My house is hell?
Tea... coffee.
What's your name?
Xu Changyang.
You've always lived in the mountains?
Eight years.
Came to the mountains when I was 10.
12.
So you're 20 this year.
It'll get cold if you don't drink it.
Didn't I say I wanted tea?
Your first choice isn't
always the right one.
What you really want is coffee.
You don't have to wash
the cup when you're done.
If you're tired, go to your room and sleep.
When you wake up, call
Qingtian if you need me.
Going to see Qingtian this late?
Yeah, he's definitely still awake.
I'm off.
Lang Di, you can't just get rid of me.
Sister Lan said you have a new assistant.
What kind of considerate person
could you find in the village?
They're all just a bunch of rough guys.
How could they possibly take care of you?
I told Sister Lan to let me go.
But Sister Lan insisted on
keeping me with the film crew.
If you just say the word...
I'd run over there even if the
mountain road had a thousand turns.
If you came, I'd have to take care of you.
Just stay put with the crew.
I'll be back next week.
There's always another
'next week.' I don't want that.
Are you coming or not?
Oh, I hear someone talking.
Lang Di, what are you doing?
Are you really getting rid of me?
Sister Lan said you have a new assistant.
Is it true?
Alright, stop the drama.
You sound like you're
in a palace drama.
I can go too.
The fresh aroma is coming out.
Lower the heat, lower the heat.
Is Teacher Fu's place far from here?
Not too far, not too close.
How are you so sure
he's not asleep this late?
It's like this every time
we come to the mountains.
The first night, he always
drags me along to roast tea.
This time, it's because you're here...
that he told me to come
over tomorrow night instead.
The tea you roast is delicious.
You must have tried it, right?
No, you just gave me coffee.
That's good, master.
Okay.
[I'm guessing he's blocking
the person he just had sex with]
Qingtian, Teacher Fu.
So many people.
Hey, Azha.
Have a seat.
Qingtian, is this your brother?
The big star is good-looking, huh?
Do you know him?
What's the deal with you two?
Drink up, drink up.
Teacher Fu, is this batch done roasting?
With Molie's liquor, once you
have a sip, you have to keep drinking.
Can you handle it?
Keep drinking until when?
Until you pass out.
Teacher Fu.
Hmm?
Is that the tea you picked yesterday?
I always see you in the media.
Teacher Fu.
Yes?
The tea you gave Qingtian before...
I really liked it.
Sister Lan liked it a lot too.
Oh? Which one did you like?
It was a ripe pu'er.
Sister Lan and I both
have sensitive stomachs.
So ripe tea suits us better.
The aroma is coming out.
Teacher Fu, come have a drink.
I'll toast to you.
Thank you.
Want to try?
Sure.
Put on the gloves.
How long does it take to roast one batch?
At least half an hour.
It's hard work.
That's why Qingtian can't do it.
He always makes Teacher Fu and me do it.
It smells amazing.
This is the first time I've smelled
the aroma of tea at this stage.
It smells even better than it tastes.
The aroma is different at every stage.
I'll roll the tea I roasted myself.
You teach him.
Do you always fight with your
brother over things at home?
Do I look like I have
nothing better to do at home?
Shake it. Let the heat out.
Save this batch of tea for me.
- I'll drink it myself.
- It's very expensive.
- I'll pay.
- I'm not kidding.
The tea Qingtian had me roast...
the leaves are all top-grade.
The market price is 80,000 per kilogram.
At auction, it could go for a million.
And if you say I'm the
one who roasted it...
it would sell for at least ten million.
So, I'll sell it to you for eight million.
You'll make a clean two million profit.
Hey, that's expensive.
When are you two having kids?
Tomorrow is the 15th.
No one's going to sleep, huh.
That's how it is during
the spring tea season.
We roast tea until dawn.
Go back, get some sleep.
Then go up the mountain to pick more tea.
If you're tired, go back and sleep.
What about you?
I'll walk you back.
How can you come to Molie and not drink?
Have one drink. I'll take you back after.
Alright.
What kind of liquor?
Mulberry wine.
Let's do an 'aerial refueling'.
Aerial refueling.
Aerial refueling. Chug!
Chug!
This isn't fruit wine.
It's mulberry baijiu. 52% alcohol.
This shirt...
Hey, my brother's a one-drink wonder.
Don't be ridiculous.
Here, you take it.
See you tomorrow.
A call is coming in. Don't answer it.
We'll drink more later.
Okay.
Shi Yuhao, you bastard.
Come on, drink.
Lie down.
When he drinks too much,
he thinks he's the boss.
Shi Yuhao, you bastard.
Still feeling sick?
Trash can.
Qingtian, the trash can.
You were pretty young
seven years ago, weren't you?
I'm only a year older than you.
My brother is never short
of people around him.
I've never felt that
he's truly loved anyone.
He seems to have a very
complicated history with Shi Yuhao.
But I don't think he ever truly loved him.
There's a lot of gossip online.
They say he started avoiding Shi
Yuhao as a form of self-preservation.
Because he knew he would fall in love.
And he was afraid of falling in love.
That's why he avoided him.
How many people really
understand love at that age?
A moment of impulse...
a fleeting crush.
Everyone goes through that.
Changyang.
I consider you a good friend.
So I want to give you a piece of advice.
Ever since Shi Yuhao...
my brother won't let
himself get hurt again.
You need to know your limits.
He's asleep.
Let me help you straighten him out.
Just let him be.
You should go back and rest.
We have to go up the mountain tomorrow.
- I'm leaving.
- Help me draw the curtains.
I'm out of face masks.
Lend me a face mask.
What's your name?
Me?
My name is Qi Haoyu.
Brother Guo.
Brother Guo lent Qi Haoyu one
face mask. When will it be returned?
Three days. I just placed an order.
It'll arrive in three days.
You have to give me back the same brand.
Then I'll place another order.
Bro.
He's the actor who has scenes with me.
Han Lu. You two said hi
in the group chat, right?
He seemed pretty
friendly in the group chat.
He's pretty friendly to me too.
Then what did I do to get on his bad side?
Do you understand the
lines for the next scene?
It's written in the director's notes.
Just because it's written
doesn't mean I understand it.
Do you get it?
Explain it to me.
Existence is existence.
That's a very extreme perspective.
My appearance is a form of existence.
Whether it's extreme
or not is your judgment.
My existence has nothing
to do with your judgment.
This flavor is low-grade.
But my judgment can't
change the fact that it's coffee.
Existence is existence.
Understand now?
You don't speak like a normal person.
What's so low-class about it?
It tastes pretty good.
[TN: He's looking up a comment section about
the actor passed out next to him and his "ex"]
[The comments are discussing the two of them
reuiniting on the variety show scheduled to film]
[Some fans are very "leave him alone," some fans
are excited about them getting back together]
[Some fans say "no way it will ever happen," some
are like "I heard his manager blah blah blah"]
[Some fans are talking about it from an economic
perspective, it just goes on and on and on]
What time is it?
4:00.
It's still early.
In the afternoon.
I slept from last night
until this afternoon?
You can't remember a thing after drinking?
- Yeah.
- You really were drinking.
Mmm.
What's this?
My clothes.
Are you sore?
It's your first time roasting tea.
It'd be weird if you weren't.
Want to sleep some more?
I could sleep a little longer.
What are you doing?
What do you want to do?
Shouldn't I be the one asking you that?
Lie on your stomach.
I haven't showered yet.
I'm allergic to a lot of essential oils.
You won't be allergic to tea tree oil.
Ow, ow, ow, that hurts!
Wow, your technique is
pretty good. Did you study this?
I once saved the last
wolf in these mountains.
Have you ever saved a bear?
I'm saving one right now.
Hold still, big bear.
Why was it the last wolf?
The year I first came to these mountains,
there were still wolves here.
Later, the locals started
putting poison on their poultry.
Any wolf that ate it would be poisoned.
When one wolf died,
the others would come and eat its carcass.
That's how the entire pack was wiped out.
I came across one of them on the mountain.
I actually used tea tree oil to
try and counteract the poison.
I never found out if it survived.
I never saw it again.
So, to me, that was the last wolf.
When a wolf dies, it gets eaten.
When a person dies, they get buried.
That's the progress of civilization.
Not necessarily.
Civilization can regress at any moment.
It depends on where a person dies.
And under what circumstances.
Survival is the basic
instinct of all living things.
You can see it everywhere in this forest.
This instinct is everywhere.
Love is a human instinct.
I don't know what counts as love.
You should know all about it.
I don't know either.
You used too much brute
force roasting the tea.
I do everything that way.
I'll call you when dinner's ready.
I'll help.
Go play on your phone.
Or go get the drone
back from Qingtian's place.
Why were you carrying a drone yesterday?
I was going to take
you to film the sunrise.
But then you got drunk.
So that drone yesterday was yours?
Yeah.
So you filmed me throwing up, too?
Did I?
The footage is on my computer.
My door is locked.
The key?
It's hanging right next to my door.
Hey!
Are all you celebrities this
worried about your image?
If you dare post that
embarrassing footage of me,
you're dead meat.
Eat slowly.
When you're done, I'll
take you out for a reshoot.
Hello?
Where are you?
Just passed Xigui.
You'll be here before dark.
(Someone will always come into your life.)